Now it's time to warm up the lips.
The first thing that you want to do is you want to think in terms of creating voiceless sounds through your lips.
I want you to blow air through your lips, just allowing them to flutter.
Sometimes you might do that when you get frustrated, you might blow air through your lips.
And you want to do that 4, 5, 6 times, allowing your lips to flutter.
I'm sorry, that makes my nose itch, that fluttering.
The next thing that you want to do is blow vibration through.
So the first time through we just have that little tickle-y flutter, and now we really want to put a hard, vibrating sound on our lip, where you really get a vibration, you really get a nose itching kind of really vibrating feeling.
So a light flutter, a voiceless sound, and then a hard-voiced flutter of the lips.
That's the first thing that you want to do to get your lips warmed up.